

博士研究

博士题目:"面向车联网的移动云网络资源管理与优化研究",来自"国家自然科学基金项目"

My research examined the use of ELW pulses from a mode-locked source array inducted through transuranic crystals to observe entanglement on supraquantum structures. Theoretical advancements included prediction of quantum resonance phenomena including the possibility of resonance cascades. I was motivated to conduct this doctoral research due to my passion for teleportation of matter and I believe I have laid the foundation for further experimental validation and development of practical outcomes.

项目经历

Current, from Jan 1995 (FT)

Black Mesa Research Facility Team Leader (Anomalous Materials)

As part of this promotion, I began conducting nuclear and subatomic research in the Anomalous Materials department. My team and I are particularly interested in dimensionality and its interaction with spacetime. The focus is on practical outcomes and applications in teleportation and communication with distal locations.

Feb 1991 -- Jan 1995 (FT)

Black Mesa Research Facility Level 3 Research Associate

This position involved transitioning from purely theoretical work to experimental applications utilising the immense resources of Black Mesa. The transition required an initial learning curve in hazard containment, health and safety procedures and operating experimental infrastructure. Manipulating valves, carts, buttons, levers, etc considerably increased my physical fitness.

Jul 1982 -- Dec 1984 (PT)

WashPests Limited Pest Control Technician

In this summer job I was tasked with helping eradicate pests from industrial areas. Work involved setting traps, spraying and physical eradication. I received praise for reaching difficult areas and my innovative use of a crowbar to assist in my work.

ペ │ 北京市海淀区西土城路 10 号

L +86-15501081468

houlu8674@bupt.edu.cn
https://www.lucima.cn

https://github.com/houluy

https://www.linkedin.com/in/houlu

guaguade astroooooo

教育经历

2014 -- 2019 工学博士

智能计算与通信实验室

北京邮电大学

2010 -- 2014 工学学士

信息与通信工程学院 北京邮电大学

获奖情况

2017 国家奖学金

北京邮电大学智能计算与通信实验室

2018 第二届良飞奖

北京邮电大学智能计算与通信实验室

编程技能

精通 Python, Node.js

熟悉 C, C++, MATLAB, LATEX

了解 Go, Rust

沟通

Posters Poster at the Meeting of the American

Physical Society -- 1985

技能

Goal Oriented

I believe in action over long-winded discussions. I listen to everyone's viewpoints and use my judgement to immediately act based on consensus to achieve goals quickly and efficiently.

Physical Dexterity

Manual manipulation of experimental equipment and training within Black Mesa (e.g. the Hazard Course) have contributed to an enjoyment of working with my hands.

Passionate

I have been interested in theoretical physics such as quantum mechanics and relativity from an early age. My education and research have cemented this interest into a passion. I greatly enjoy carrying out fundamental physics research with potential practical applications.

已发表论文

Kan Zheng, Lu Hou, Hanling Meng, Qiang Zheng, Ning Lu, Lei Lei, ``Soft-defined heterogeneous vehicular network: architecture and challenges," IEEE Network, vol. 30, no. 4, July 2016, pp. 72-80.(IF = 7.23)

Lu Hou, Shaohang Zhao, Xiong Xiong, Kan Zheng, Periklis Chatzimisios, M. Shamim Hossain, Wei Xiang, "Internet of things cloud: architecture and implementation," IEEE Communications Magazine, vol. 54, no. 12, Dec. 2016, pp. 32–39. (IF = 10.435)

Lu Hou, Shaohang Zhao, Xing Li, Periklis Chatzimisios, Kan Zheng, "Design and implementation of application programming interface for Internet of things cloud," International Journal of Network Management, vol. 27, no. 3, June 2016. (IF = 1.118)

Lu Hou, Kan Zheng, Periklis Chatzimisios, Yi Feng, "A continuous—time Markov decision process—based resource allocation scheme in vehicu—lar cloud for mobile video services," Computer Communications, vol. 118, Mar. 2018, pp. 140–147. (IF = 3.338)

Lu Hou, Lei Lei, Kan Zheng, "Design on publish/subscribe message dissemination for vehicular networks with mobile edge computing," 2017 IEEE GLOBECOM, Dec. 2017

Xiong Xiong, Lu Hou, Kan Zheng, Wei Xiang, M. Shamim Hossain, and Sk Md Mizanur Rahman, "SMDP-based radio resource allocation scheme in software-defined internet of things networks," IEEE Sensors Journal vol. 16, no. 20, June 2016, pp. 7304–7314. (IF = 2.512)

Xiong Xiong, Lu Hou, Long Zhao, "A Group-Based Massive Multiple Access Scheme in Cellular M2M Networks," Computer Communications, vol. 121, May. 2018, pp. 44–49. (IF = 3.338)

1996 doi:10.1021/jp951483+ 1990 doi:10.1139/p90-097 1986 doi:10.1139/v86-297

1986 doi:10.1103/PhysRevA.34.2329



DOCTORAL RESEARCH

"Research on Resource Management and Optimization of Mobile Cloud Networks for Internet of Vehicles"

My research examined the use of ELW pulses from a mode-locked source array inducted through transuranic crystals to observe entanglement on supraquantum structures. Theoretical advancements included prediction of quantum resonance phenomena including the possibility of resonance cascades. I was motivated to conduct this doctoral research due to my passion for teleportation of matter and I believe I have laid the foundation for further experimental validation and development of practical outcomes.

WORK EXPERIENCE

CURRENT, FROM JAN 1995 (FT)

Black Mesa Research Facility Team Leader (Anomalous Materials)

As part of this promotion, I began conducting nuclear and subatomic research in the Anomalous Materials department. My team and I are particularly interested in dimensionality and its interaction with spacetime. The focus is on practical outcomes and applications in teleportation and communication with distal locations.

FEB 1991 - JAN 1995 (FT)

Black Mesa Research Facility Level 3 Research Associate

This position involved transitioning from purely theoretical work to experimental applications utilising the immense resources of Black Mesa. The transition required an initial learning curve in hazard containment, health and safety procedures and operating experimental infrastructure. Manipulating valves, carts, buttons, levers, etc considerably increased my physical fitness.

JUL 1982 – DEC 1984 (PT)

WashPests Limited Pest Control Technician

In this summer job I was tasked with helping eradicate pests from industrial areas. Work involved setting traps, spraying and physical eradication. I received praise for reaching difficult areas and my innovative use of a crowbar to assist in my work.

No. 10, Xitucheng Road, Haidian District,
Beijing

+86-15501081468

houlu8674@bupt.edu.cn

https://www.lucima.cn

https://github.com/username

https://www.linkedin.com/in/username

guaguade

astroooooo

EDUCATION

1986 – 1990 **Doctor of Philosophy**

Theoretical Physics

Massachusetts Institute of Technology

1985 Master of Science

FIRST CLASS HONOURS
Theoretical Physics

Massachusetts Institute of Technology

1982 – 1984 Bachelor of Physics

Department of Physics
The University of Washington

AWARDS

1985 Faculty of Science Masters Scholarship

Massachusetts Institute of Technology

1983 **Top Achiever Award – Physics** The University of Washington

COMPUTER SKILLS

BEGINNER Java, MS DOS

INTERMEDIATE Javascript, Python, HTML, CSS,

Microsoft Windows

Computer Hardware & Support

EXPERT Perl, Unix, LATEX

COMMUNICATION SKILLS

CONFERENCES Oral Presentation at the Annual MIT

Theoretical Physics Conference - 1987

POSTERS Poster at the Meeting of the American

Physical Society - 1985

SKILLS

Goal Oriented

I believe in action over long-winded discussions. I listen to everyone's viewpoints and use my judgement to immediately act based on consensus to achieve goals quickly and efficiently.

Physical Dexterity

Manual manipulation of experimental equipment and training within Black Mesa (e.g. the Hazard Course) have contributed to an enjoyment of working with my hands.

Passionate

I have been interested in theoretical physics such as quantum mechanics and relativity from an early age. My edu-

cation and research have cemented this interest into a passion. I greatly enjoy carrying out fundamental physics research with potential practical applications.

PUBLICATIONS

Freeman, G. R. (1996). Chemistry of Multiply Charged Negative Molecular Ions and Clusters in the Gas Phase: Terrestrial and in Intense Galactic Magnetic Fields. *The Journal of Physical Chemistry*, 100(II), 433I-4338.

Jacobsen, F. M., Gee, N., **Freeman, G. R.** (1986). Electron mobility in liquid krypton as function of density, temperature, and electric field strength. *Physical Review A*, *34*(3): 2329-2335.

1996 doi:10.1021/jp951483+

1990 doi:10.1139/p90-097

1986 doi:10.1139/v86-297

1986 doi:10.1103/PhysRevA.34.2329

First author publications in **bold**